There's something quite surreal about seeing people on the internet say she's in a room full of dummies.
There's something quite surreal about people feeling like they would have watched an intellectual conversation
when they do not watch intellectual conversations because they are not intellectuals.
And there's something very real about knowing that and thus surreptitiously sliding in the truth,
facts, history, and information into spaces where it rarely exists.
And the actual sacrifice that it takes to envelop yourself in ignorance in order to do so for the greater good.
I appreciate all of those who understand what that is.
How taxing and exhausting it is.
And anyone who is not able to see that, who seems to think that their lack of intellect is somehow invalidating of my work on Surrounded,
those people need to do further exploration, examination, and analysis of what we're surrounded by.
Because those people are a true representation of where we are.
And I hope I gave you some tools and some tips on how to have the next conversation at your Thanksgiving dinner.